<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meta on umoci</title>
    <link>https://umo.ci/meta/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meta on umoci</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://umo.ci/meta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>https://umo.ci/meta/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://umo.ci/meta/changelog/</guid>
      <description>Changelog All notable changes to this project will be documented in this file.
The format is based on Keep a Changelog and this project adheres to Semantic Versioning.
Unreleased umoci has been adopted by the Open Container Initative as a reference implementation of the OCI Image Specification. This will have little impact on the roadmap or scope of umoci, but it does further solidify umoci as a useful piece of &amp;ldquo;boring container infrastructure&amp;rdquo; that can be used to build larger systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribution Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://umo.ci/meta/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://umo.ci/meta/contributing/</guid>
      <description>Contribution Guidelines If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, you&amp;rsquo;re likely interested in contributing to this project. That&amp;rsquo;s great! The intention of this document is to describe the basic requirements and rules-of-thumb for contributions.
Security Issues If you are reporting a security issue, please do not create an issue or file a pull request on GitHub. Instead, disclose the issue by sending an email to mailto:security@opencontainers.org. If you feel it is necessary you may also encrypt your email with Pretty Good Privacy (PGP) using the set of PGP keys listed in the umoci keyring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governance</title>
      <link>https://umo.ci/meta/governance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://umo.ci/meta/governance/</guid>
      <description>Governance Model umoci is an OCI project, and is thus governed under the OCI Charter. ยง5(b)(viii) of the Charter tasks the maintainers of each OCI Project with:
 Creating, maintaining and enforcing governance guidelines for the TDC [of that OCI Project], approved by the maintainers, and which shall be posted visibly for the TDC [of that OCI Project].
 This document describes the governance rules for umoci, and is the authortiative document that describes the governance procedure for umoci.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Procedure</title>
      <link>https://umo.ci/meta/releases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://umo.ci/meta/releases/</guid>
      <description>Release Procedure This document describes the procedure for preparing and publishing an umoci release. Note that in order for a release of umoci to be approved, it must follow the approval procedure described in GOVERNANCE.md.
Changelog Before anything else, you must update the CHANGELOG.md to match the release. This boils down to adding a new header underneath the &amp;ldquo;Unreleased&amp;rdquo; header so that all of the changes are listed as being part of the new release.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>